Guide to the Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 records, 2005- 2007; 3185-015; 28.73 cubic feet 26 boxes
  - Series 1: General Correspondence, 2005-2007
    - General Correspondence (Seattle Housing Authority [3rd Qtr]-International Minutes), 2006 (Box 7)
    - General Correspondence (PSBT Correspondence-K), 2007 (Box 8)
    - General Correspondence (L-Sea Mar [Dec]), 2007 (Box 9)
    - General Correspondence (Seattle Housing Authority - Willapa Harbor Hospital), 2007 (Box 10)
    - General Correspondence (Political Action Committee-International Minutes), 2007 (Box-folder 11/1-12)
  - Series 2: Negotiations, 2005-2007
    - Negotiations A-U, 2005 (Box-folder 11/13-35)
    - Negotiations (V-Willapa Bargain [May 17]), 2005 (Box 12)
    - Negotiations (Willapa Bargain [May 11]-M), 2005-2006 (Box 13)
    - Negotiations (A-COM), 2006 (Box 20)
    - Negotiations (O-VMC), 2006 (Box 14)
    - Negotiations (W-WPAS), 2006 (Box 15)
    - Negotiations (WPAS-Senior Life Resources [1/2]), 2006-2007 (Box 16)
    - Negotiations (Senior Life Resources [2/2]-W), 2007 (Box-folder 17/1-7)
  - Series 3: Disputes and Grievances, 2005-2007
    - Disputes and Grievances (A-Ce), 2005 (Box-folder 17/8-50)
    - Disputes and Grievances (Ch-Mi), 2005 (Box 18)
    - Disputes and Grievances (Mi-We), 2005 (Box 19)
    - Disputes and Grievances (We-Fe), 2005-2006 (Box 21)
    - Disputes and Grievances (Fin-Mor), 2006 (Box 22)
    - Disputes and Grievances (Nam-Bar), 2006-2007 (Box 23)
    - Disputes and Grievances (Bar-Jas), 2007 (Box 24)
    - Disputes and Grievances (Kor-Sul), 2007 (Box 25)
    - Disputes and Grievances (Lau-Wei), 2007 (Box 26)
- Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 records, 2008-2010; 3185-016; 18.24 cubic feet (16 boxes)
  General correspondence of the the union.
  No restrictions on access.
  Libby Alejandro, OPEIU Local 8 and Cindy Shu, OPEIU Local 8
  - General correspondence (A-H), 2008 (Box 1)
  - General correspondence (K-P), 2008 (Box 2)
  - General correspondence (Sc-Sp), 2008 (Box 3)
  - General correspondence (T-W), 2008 (Box 4)
    Top & Bottom Drawer (PSBT/Itn’l Correspo/PSBT/Western States)
  - General correspondence, Chron reps files (B-V), 2008 (Box 5)
  - General correspondence (A-I), 2009 (Box 6)
  - General correspondence (K-O), 2009 (Box 7)
  - General Correspondence (P – Sea Mar [Jan-Nov]), 2009 (Box 8)
  - General Correspondence (Sea Mar [Dec]-U), 2009 (Box 9)
  - General Correspondence (V-W), 2009 (Box 10)
  - General Correspondence, Chron reps files (Sea Mar [Dec]-U), 2009 (Box 11)
  - General Correspondence (A-KGH), 2010 (Box 12)
  - General Correspondence (King County-O), 2010 (Box 13)
  - General Correspondence (PRMCE-Sea Mar), 2010 (Box 14)
  - General Correspondence (SHA-W), 2010 (Box 15)
  - General Correspondence, 2010; Top & Bottom Drawer (Chron Reps file/Associate App 2001-2010/sign in/PSBT/Itn’l Correspo/PSBT/Western States) (Box 16)